Your lighter is...
당신의 라이터는...
Ronson diesel lighter.
론슨 디젤 라이터.
Made in America.
미국에서 만든.
How are you, friend?
잘 지내요, 친구?
Two!
둘!
Don't look there.
거기 보지 마세요.
They are connected.
그들은 연결되어 있습니다.
Chief.
셰프.
We can't hear what they say here.
여기서는 그들이 말하는 것을 들을 수 없습니다.
What if it was closer?
더 가까웠으면 어땠을까?
No need to listen to what they say.
그들이 말하는 것을 들을 필요가 없습니다.
We must not act rashly.
우리는 경솔하게 행동해서는 안 됩니다.
After they separated,
그들은 헤어진 후,
we will also separate.
우리도 헤어질 거예요.
You and A-Chuan...
당신과 A-Chuan...
With Tian.
티안과 함께.
Me and Xiao Lai Zi,
나와 Xiao Lai Zi,
and people who work together,
그리고 함께 일하는 사람들,
understand.
이해하다.
Go away.
저리 가요.
Good.
좋은.
Border regional government
국경지방정부
after stopping the circulation of French money
프랑스 화폐 유통을 중단한 후
and replace it with fringe money.
그리고 그것을 부가 화폐로 대체하세요.
The border area's financial work has reversed the situation
국경지역의 금융업무로 상황이 역전됐다
social stability in border areas
국경 지역의 사회적 안정
and community life
그리고 공동체 생활
has also improved a lot.
도 많이 좋아졌습니다.
It's just that I didn't expect it
단지 예상하지 못했을 뿐이야
in the marginal money design and printing team
한계돈 디자인 및 인쇄팀에서
in the money design and printing team.
돈 디자인 및 인쇄 팀에서.
These two spies
이 두 스파이
is there a person named wild goose?
기러기라는 사람이 있나요?
Correct.
옳은.
There is one more.
하나 더 있습니다.
Codenamed Xi Que.
코드네임 Xi Que.
Xi Que?
시퀘?
My Special Case Team colleagues and I
나와 특례팀 동료들
I've been investigating them for so long,
나는 오랫동안 그들을 조사해왔습니다.
unexpectedly before being arrested, they leaked information,
체포되기 전 예상치 못하게 정보를 유출했고,
they ran away
그들은 도망갔다
also took away two coins
동전 두 개도 가져갔어
and a formula for printing money
그리고 돈을 인쇄하는 공식
we tracked it all the way.
우리는 그것을 끝까지 추적했습니다.
Found traces of them in Jinan.
지난에서 그 흔적을 찾았습니다.
Unexpectedly, just shot
의외로 그냥 쐈어
they are blurred again.
다시 흐려졌습니다.
I chased Xi Que
나는 Xi Qu를 쫓아갔다.
arrived in Shanghai
상하이에 도착했다
This is a magpie.
이것은 까치입니다.
And also the data
그리고 데이터도
did you manage to catch it?
잡을 수 있었나요?
a little more.
좀 더.
He remains vague.
그는 여전히 모호하다.
I'm hurt too.
나도 상처받았어.
Can only blame myself for being useless.
쓸모없다고 스스로를 비난할 수 밖에 없습니다.
You can find spies,
스파이를 찾을 수 있고,
it's not easy anymore.
더 이상 쉽지 않습니다.
The situation is urgent.
상황이 긴급합니다.
I don't understand Shanghai either.
상하이도 이해가 안 돼요.
So just can use
그래서 그냥 사용할 수 있습니다
emergency contact procedures
비상 연락 절차
previously,
이전에,
I hope you get your help
도움을 받으시길 바랍니다
I'll be right away
바로 갈게요
gathered several colleagues in charge of the intelligence station,
정보국을 담당하는 동료 몇 명을 모아서
to discuss this together.
이것을 함께 논의하기 위해.
The magpie's left hand and stomach had been shot.
까치의 왼손과 배에 총이 맞았습니다.
I think he must be hiding somewhere to treat his wounds.
내 생각엔 그 사람이 상처를 치료하기 위해 어딘가에 숨어 있는 게 틀림없는 것 같아.
What are your plans after this?
이후 계획은 어떻게 되나요?
Wait until my wound heals,
내 상처가 아물 때까지 기다리세요.
I want to join your action.
나는 당신의 행동에 동참하고 싶습니다.
Don't worry, treat your wounds first.
걱정하지 말고 먼저 상처를 치료하세요.
Come on, follow him.
자, 그를 따라가세요.
Mother, I want to eat Tanghulu.
엄마, 나 탕후루 먹고 싶어요.
Good.
좋은.
How much does one Tang Hu Lu cost?
Tang Hu Lu 하나의 비용은 얼마입니까?
Not selling, not selling.
안 팔아요, 안 팔아요.
I want to eat.
나는 먹고 싶다.
Step aside.
비켜서 다.
What is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
If you don't want to sell, don't sell.
팔기 싫으면 팔지 마세요.
I told you not to sell.
팔지 말라고 했잖아.
Why do you hit a child?
왜 애를 때리나요?
Small child, very small.
작은 아이, 아주 작은 아이.
Why do you have the heart to hit him?
왜 그를 때릴 마음이 있습니까?
Why do you hit a child?
왜 애를 때리나요?
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
Chase him.
그를 쫓아라.
Pay as needed.
필요에 따라 지불하십시오.
You're crazy, aren't you?
당신은 미쳤지, 그렇지?
not good.
안좋다.
The old road has been discovered.
오래된 도로가 발견되었습니다.
Do not move.
이동하지 않습니다.
This dragon stone table is made of fine clay.
이 용석 테이블은 고운 점토로 만들어졌습니다.
It could be said that mud is stronger than stone.
진흙은 돌보다 강하다고 할 수 있습니다.
You must not be using it properly
제대로 사용하지 말아야 합니다
can only make this crack.
이 균열만 만들 수 있습니다.
No. I mean road boss.
아뇨. 내 말은 도로 상사를 말하는 거예요.
I use it for sharpening and writing
샤프닝과 필기용으로 사용하고 있어요
not be a board cutter.
보드 커터가 되지 마세요.
How could it not be used properly?
어떻게 제대로 사용할 수 없습니까?
Moreover
게다가
your maintenance costs
유지 관리 비용
a bit too expensive.
좀 너무 비싸요.
To repair this crack
이 균열을 수리하려면
I used stone powder to turn it into glue.
나는 돌가루를 사용하여 접착제로 만들었습니다.
For sharpening and lubricating.
연마 및 윤활용.
Then use yellow wax and ink on it
그런 다음 노란색 왁스와 잉크를 사용하십시오.
to color.
색칠하기.
Look,
바라보다,
intact as before.
이전과 마찬가지로 그대로.
Can you still see the crack?
아직도 균열이 보이나요?
Invisible.
보이지 않는.
But, Boss Lu,
하지만 루 보스,
At first, what you did to me... was interesting.
처음에는 당신이 나에게 한 짓이... 흥미로웠어요.
What's with the sound?
소리는 어떻게 되나요?
cut off without holes
구멍 없이 잘라내다
but I made it crack after using it a few times.
그런데 몇 번 사용하다 보니 금이 가더군요.
Don't be afraid to sell fake goods.
가짜 상품을 판매하는 것을 두려워하지 마십시오.
No, how do you talk?
아니, 어떻게 얘기해요?
Tuan Lu,
투안 루,
I've looked after your business many times.
나는 여러 번 당신의 사업을 돌보았습니다.
If you sell me fake goods again,
또 가짜 물건을 팔면
That's too unkind.
너무 불친절해요.
You two
너희 둘
do you want me to do business?
내가 사업하기를 바라나요?
The old way
옛날 방식
application submitted to the organization
조직에 제출된 신청서
Is there any reply from the organization?
기관에서는 답변이 없나요?
Saying this inkstone is fake.
이 벼루는 가짜라고 하네요.
Do not be angry
화 내지 마
quickly tell me
빨리 말해줘
your request
당신의 요청
approved by the organization.
조직의 승인을 받았습니다.
You can keep lurking.
계속 숨어있을 수 있습니다.
A little plan.
작은 계획.
Don't break it
부수지 마세요
I've spent a lot of money to fix it.
그걸 고치려고 돈을 많이 썼어요.
Then got the left twin
그다음 왼쪽 쌍둥이를 얻었어
What is the organization saying?
조직에서는 뭐라고 말하나요?
No, what are you doing?
아니, 뭐하는 거야?
Quickly tell me.
빨리 말해주세요.
The purpose of the organization is
조직의 목적은
you should be more careful.
좀 더 조심해야 해.
You can do experiments in peace,
안심하고 실험을 할 수 있습니다.
observe the reaction.
반응을 관찰하세요.
Don't rush to success
성공을 위해 서두르지 마세요
don't let him know your intentions.
그에게 당신의 의도를 알리지 마십시오.
Understand.
이해하다.
There is still one important thing
아직 중요한게 하나 남아있어요
organization.
조직.
Asking you to control the husband and wife relationship.
남편과 아내의 관계를 통제하라고 요구합니다.
Distance and boundaries
거리와 경계
don't go too far
너무 멀리 가지 마세요
Also don't get too close.
또한 너무 가까이 가지 마세요.
Far will be suspicious,
멀리서는 의심스러울 것이다.
close would be dangerous.
가까이 가면 위험할 것 같아요.
You must remember these eight words.
이 여덟 단어를 기억해야 합니다.
I will remember it.
나는 그것을 기억할 것이다.
Both of us
우리 둘 다
it's been noisy lately
최근에 시끄러웠어
I happen to be able to take advantage of this opportunity
우연히 이 기회를 활용할 수 있게 됐어요
stubbornness
고집
I understand.
이해합니다.
Oh yes
바로 이거 야
let me show you something.
뭔가 보여드리죠.
What is this?
이게 뭔가요?
The document you recorded
당신이 기록한 문서
recorded a large number of acts of betrayal by the Chongqing government.
충칭 정부의 수많은 배신 행위를 기록했습니다.
As if preparing to receive...
마치 받을 준비를 하는 것처럼..
Japan's proposal to sign a defense treaty.
일본의 방위조약 체결 제안.
Accepting the placement of Japanese troops on Chinese soil.
중국 땅에 일본군의 배치를 받아들인다.
Even recognizing the fake Manchurian state, reorganizing the Chinese government.
가짜 만주국가까지 인정하고, 중국 정부를 개편한다.
After publication,
출판 후,
Domestic and international public opinion was in an uproar.
국내외 여론은 들끓었다.
Unanimously condemned Chiang Kai-shek's treasonous policies.
장제스의 반역적 정책을 만장일치로 비난했다.
old road,
오래된 길,
can you give me this newspaper?
이 신문 좀 줄래?
I'm useful.
나는 유용하다.
OK, just keep it.
좋아요, 그냥 보관하세요.
Correct.
옳은.
There's one more thing,
한 가지 더 있어요.
I feel like I should tell you.
꼭 말해야 할 것 같은 기분이 들어요.
Today I met a colleague
오늘 나는 동료를 만났습니다.
met, he told me,
만났고, 그가 나에게 말했다.
there are two military spies hiding in Yan'an,
옌안에는 두 명의 군 스파이가 숨어 있습니다.
steal coins there
거기서 동전을 훔쳐
and printing paper.
그리고 인쇄용지.
Zhu Yuhua also told me,
Zhu Yuhua도 나에게 말했습니다.
said that Shan's plan also planned to counterfeit foreign currency.
Shan의 계획은 외화 위조도 계획하고 있다고 말했습니다.
What do you think of these two special agents
이 두 특수요원에 대해 어떻게 생각하시나요?
is it related to the Shan Project?
Shan 프로젝트와 관련이 있나요?
Still not sure.
아직도 확실하지 않습니다.
Tomorrow morning
내일 아침
I will meet with several people in charge of intelligence posts
정보소 담당자 여러 명을 만나겠습니다
to meet at the Hai Zhong Xian Tea House to discuss this.
이 문제를 논의하기 위해 Hai Zhong Xian Tea House에서 만나기로 했습니다.
Tomorrow you have to pay attention
내일은 집중해야 해
business movements and military bases.
비즈니스 움직임과 군사 기지.
Do a good job of peripheral security.
주변 보안을 잘 수행하십시오.
Good.
좋은.
There's one more thing.
한 가지가 더 있습니다.
Don't smoke anymore
더 이상 담배를 피우지 마세요
Your eyes are quite sharp too.
당신의 눈도 꽤 날카롭습니다.
This
이것
friend from Yan'an today.
오늘 옌안에서 온 친구.
Kak Tian!
칵 티안!
Kak Tian.
칵 티안.
What is your assignment to Shanghai?
상하이에서의 임무는 무엇입니까?
Apart from people who
그런 사람들 외에도
the person who contacted you,
당신에게 연락한 사람,
is there anyone else?
또 누구 있어?
Mine.
내 거.
My job
내 일
What's that?
그게 뭐야?
This is a war against Japan to save the country.
이것은 나라를 구하기 위한 일본과의 전쟁이다.
Mine.
내 거.
Contact?
연락하다?
Is Chinese
중국인인가
I know you can't say anything
당신이 아무 말도 할 수 없다는 걸 알아요
It doesn't matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
We've followed
우리는 따라왔다
your previous contact.
이전 연락처.
Following the roots of this plant
이 식물의 뿌리를 따라
will get a lot of information.
많은 정보를 얻게 됩니다.
Now it's you or not,
이제 당신이냐 아니냐
Up to you.
당신한테 달렸습니다.
You
너
won't work
작동하지 않습니다
you just see
너는 방금 본다
salah.
살라.
You didn't see either.
당신도 보지 못했습니다.
I'm about to die
나는 곧 죽을 것입니다
still loud-mouthed
아직도 입이 크다
today just throw him here
오늘은 그냥 여기 던져
tomorrow call 2 swords to clean up the body.
내일 검 2개를 불러 시체를 청소하세요.
Good
좋은
I have a request.
부탁이 있습니다.
Say it.
말해.
I want to smoke.
나는 담배를 피우고 싶다.
No need.
필요 없음.
It's in my pocket
내 주머니 안에 있어
or smoke from the hometown.
아니면 고향에서 담배를 피워요.
Fragrant
향기로운
I really don't understand these CCP people
나는 중국 공산당 사람들이 정말 이해가 안 돼요.
You're already dying, still haven't smoked a good cigarette.
당신은 이미 죽어가고 있고, 아직도 좋은 담배를 피우지 못했습니다.
I can
저 할 수 있어요
already home?
벌써 집에?
Tuan Shan Xia.
투안샨샤.
Owned by Han Lu.
한루 소유.
How is your health condition?
건강상태는 어떻습니까?
It's much better.
훨씬 나아졌습니다.
Thank You.
감사합니다.
I know you have experienced suffering
나는 당신이 고통을 경험했다는 것을 알고 있습니다
never bothered you
결코 당신을 귀찮게 하지 않았다
today after finding out you came home from the hospital,
오늘 당신이 병원에서 집에 왔다는 소식을 듣고
I specially came to celebrate.
특별히 축하하러 왔습니다.
That's right, Miss Han Lu.
그렇죠, 한루 선생님.
Tuan Shan Xia.
투안샨샤.
I also prepared special champagne for you.
당신을 위해 특별한 샴페인도 준비했어요.
Thank you for Mr. Shan Xia's kindness.
Shan Xia 선생님의 친절에 감사드립니다.
However, recently,
그러나 최근에는
I want to be alone.
혼자 있고 싶어.
For Han Lu,
한루의 경우,
I have also experienced death.
나 역시 죽음을 경험한 적이 있다.
Death is what made me start a new life.
죽음은 나에게 새로운 삶을 시작하게 해주었다.
I hope...
나는 희망...
Miss Han Lu can also welcome a new birth.
한루 선생님도 새로운 탄생을 맞이할 수 있습니다.
It is clear,
분명하다,
pkc that cooperates with Tian,
Tian과 협력하는 pkc,
bernama Lu Yousheng.
베르나마 루 유셩.
People who know him call him old road.
그를 아는 사람들은 그를 옛길이라고 부른다.
He owns a shop called Yumo
그는 Yumo라는 가게를 운영하고 있습니다.
the shop owner is named Yumo
가게 주인 이름은 Yumo
Yumo Painting and Calligraphy shop
Yumo 그림과 서예 가게
we still have greater achievements.
우리는 여전히 더 큰 성과를 거두었습니다.
Today as we hunker down
오늘 우리가 웅크리고 있을 때
around the bookstore
서점 주변
Section Chief Chen also happened to come
우연히 첸 과장도 왔어요
chen Jia Ping
첸 지아 핑
what did he go for
그 사람은 무엇 때문에 갔나요?
seems to be repairing an inkstone
벼루를 수리하는 것 같아요
inkstone
벼루
we asked the people around the calligraphy and painting shop again.
서예가게 주변 사람들에게 다시 물었다.
Department Head Chen was a regular customer of the shop
첸 부장은 이 가게의 단골 손님이었습니다.
come often?
자주 와?
No wonder when you're in Waitan,
당신이 Waitan에 있을 때는 당연합니다.
I feel very familiar with the old road
오래된 길에 아주 익숙한 느낌이 들어요
he must have appeared near our shop
그 사람이 우리 가게 근처에 나타난 게 틀림없어
team leader
팀 리더
it seems your previous suspicions were correct.
이전 의심이 정확한 것 같습니다.
Chen Jia Ping
첸 지아 핑
who is hiding behind this CCP.
이 중국 공산당 뒤에 누가 숨어 있는지.
This time it's for sure
이번엔 확실해
kalau Chen Jia Ping bilang
칼라우 첸 지아 핑 빌랑
he went to the old shop
그는 오래된 가게에 갔다
just to buy brushes, ink, paper and inkwells.
붓, 잉크, 종이, 잉크병을 사려고요.
Not knowing Lao Lu's true identity.
라오루의 정체를 알지 못하는 것.
How about this?
이건 어때?
Then arrest Lao Lu
그런 다음 라오루를 체포하세요
forcing him to identify Chen Jiaping
Chen Jiaping의 신원을 확인하도록 강요
facing the Communist Party
공산당과 마주하다
This trick of yours won't work
너의 이 속임수는 통하지 않을 거야
should be patient
인내심을 가져야 한다
fishing for small fish with shrimp
새우를 이용한 작은 물고기 낚시
catch small fish, catch big fish
작은 물고기 잡기, 큰 물고기 잡기
I introspect the mistakes I made,
내가 저지른 실수를 반성하고,
for being too impatient,
너무 참을성이 없어서,
after that, stay tuned.
그 후에는 계속 지켜봐 주시기 바랍니다.
Keep watching.
계속 시청하세요.
Must be very careful.
매우 조심해야 합니다.
Be patient in everything
모든 일에 인내하라
strong heart
강심장
The iron dagger was sharpened into a needle.
철 단검은 바늘로 날카롭게 만들어졌습니다.
Are you awake?
깨어있나요?
Why are you like that to me?
당신은 나에게 왜 그런가요?
Owned by Han Lu.
한루 소유.
Don't be angry.
화내지 마세요.
You are so outrageous!
당신은 정말 터무니없어요!
Why are you like that to me?
당신은 나에게 왜 그런가요?
I'm sincere with you.
나는 당신에게 진심입니다.
Absolutely no lies.
절대 거짓말이 아닙니다.
I can swear
맹세할 수 있어요
You think you do this
당신은 당신이 이것을 할 생각
can I accept you?
내가 당신을 받아도 될까요?
For Han Lu,
한루의 경우,
I hope today...
오늘은 좋겠다...
Is the beginning of
의 시작인가
new life.
새로운 삶.
New life?
새로운 삶?
You insult me
너는 나를 모욕했다
but instead talked about a new life.
대신 새로운 삶에 대해 이야기했습니다.
Owned by Han Lu.
한루 소유.
Look at it.
보세요.
This is a gift I specially prepared for you.
이건 내가 널 위해 특별히 준비한 선물이야.
A cinema especially for you.
당신을 위한 특별한 영화관.
After it finishes,
끝난 후,
will premiere here.
여기에서 초연됩니다.
And this cinema
그리고 이 영화관
can only be played over and over again.
반복해서만 재생할 수 있습니다.
All the films you starred in
당신이 출연한 모든 영화
because I know,
내가 알고 있기 때문에,
you like movies
당신은 영화를 좋아해요
movies are your life
영화는 당신의 삶이다
is everything to you
당신에겐 전부야
and I
그리고 나
I don't expect to have all of yours.
나는 당신의 모든 것을 가질 것으로 기대하지 않습니다.
I just hope
나는 단지 희망한다
behind you
너의 뒤에
secretly helping you achieve your dreams
비밀리에 당신의 꿈을 이루도록 도와주세요
This...
이것...
It's my love for you.
당신을 향한 나의 사랑입니다.
Liuli Guoguo.
Liuli Guoguo.
This is pretty good too.
이것도 꽤 좋습니다.
I like this color.
나는 이 색깔을 좋아한다.
Get out.
나가세요.
Go, go.
가, 가.
What is this?
이게 뭔가요?
Nona Hong Ling.
노나홍링.
It's been three days.
3일이 지났습니다.
Gambling debt last month,
지난달 도박빚,
last month?
지난 달?
Give me two more days.
이틀만 더 시간을 주세요.
I'll be getting paid soon.
곧 돈을 받게 될 거예요.
Salary?
샐러리?
How many hours can you jump a day?
하루에 몇 시간 정도 점프할 수 있나요?
Your salary
당신의 급여
minus the boss's bookkeeping.
상사의 장부를 뺀 것입니다.
How much do you have left?
얼마나 남았나요?
There are several guests
손님이 여럿 있어요
who owes me a tip.
나에게 팁을 빚진 사람.
You still have tips.
아직 팁이 남아 있습니다.
The spare bench soon disappeared.
예비 벤치는 곧 사라졌습니다.
Xiang... Trust me.
샹... 날 믿어요.
I will definitely...
난 꼭...
Give me a few more days
며칠만 더 시간을 주세요
I... I definitely...
난... 난 분명...
I...
나...
I'll give you three more days.
3일만 더 시간을 드릴게요.
If it is still not paid,
아직도 납부하지 않은 경우,
I sold you to the fireworks room.
내가 너를 불꽃놀이방에 팔았어.
It is clear?
분명합니까?
Road.
도로.
Only three days.
단 3일.
Nona.
노나.
Is he new?
그 사람이 새로 왔나요?
Can not?
할 수 없습니까?
Invites you to dance
당신을 댄스에 초대합니다
I can only do the simplest.
나는 가장 간단한 것만 할 수 있다.
A little plan.
작은 계획.
It doesn't matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
I teach you.
나는 당신을 가르칩니다.
Isn't this Mr. Yao?
이 분은 야오 씨 아닌가요?
Long time no see.
오랜만이에요.
Want to dance?
춤추고 싶어?
I'll accompany you to dance, okay?
내가 같이 춤추러 갈게, 알았지?
go away
저리 가요
Good.
좋은.
It's been a long time since I came.
오랜만에 왔어요.
Nona,
노나,
Want to dance to earn money.
돈을 벌기 위해 춤을 추고 싶다.
What is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
You come from the village, right?
당신은 마을에서 왔죠?
Presuming here is the market?
여기에 시장이 있다고 가정합니까?
Just opening one stall can do business.
노점 하나만 열면 장사가 가능하다.
I come from the village, why?
나는 마을에서 왔는데 왜?
You bully people.
당신은 사람들을 괴롭히는군요.
I still have to sell here
아직 여기서 팔아야 하는데
Where are you from?
어디서 오셨나요?
Don't you know the rules?
규칙을 모르시나요?
Get out.
나가세요.
I don't want to go out
나는 나가고 싶지 않다
why asked me out?
왜 나한테 데이트 신청했어?
You're still stubborn.
당신은 여전히 ​​완고한입니다.
Want to die.
죽고 싶다.
It is okay, right?
괜찮아요?
Is it hurt?
상처받았나요?
I'm about to die, I'm about to die.
나는 곧 죽을 것이다. 나는 곧 죽을 것이다.
Why are you still stunned?
왜 아직도 충격을 받았나요?
Drag this damn girl out!
이 빌어먹을 여자를 끌어내라!
go away
저리 가요
Don't touch me, I can walk alone
손대지 마 나 혼자 걸을 수 있어
what place is this? Bullying people!
여긴 무슨 곳이야? 사람들을 괴롭히는구나!
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
Did you dirty your clothes?
옷을 더럽혔나요?
You are
당신은
how much does it cost?
비용이 얼마나 드나요?
I will compensate you.
보상해 드리겠습니다.
Compensation?
보상?
Are you able to compensate?
보상해줄 수 있나요?
I have money.
나는 돈이 있습니다.
This cheongsam of mine was ordered by Hong Fuji.
이 치파오는 홍후지님이 주문하신 것입니다.
From real silk,
진짜 실크에서,
50 Yuan more.
50위안 더요.
Can't be washed either.
세탁도 안 돼요.
Like this, it's done.
이렇게 해서 끝났습니다.
You see.
알다시피.
Really rich.
정말 부자입니다.
Sixty.
육십.
Nona,
노나,
why do you carry so much money?
왜 그렇게 많은 돈을 가지고 다니나요?
Always unsafe.
항상 안전하지 않습니다.
I live there
나는 거기 산다
above and below there are dozens of houses.
위와 아래에는 수십 채의 집이 있습니다.
There is a big bakery seller.
큰 빵집 판매자가 있습니다.
As a messenger,
메신저로서,
a fortune teller with a bald head
대머리 점쟁이
there are people of all kinds.
온갖 종류의 사람들이 있어요.
Looks like there are still two pickpockets.
아직 소매치기가 두 명이나 있는 것 같습니다.
Then put this money at home,
그럼 이 돈을 집에 넣어두고
not dare.
감히.
So can only carry it.
그래서 들고 다닐 수 밖에 없습니다.
Why do you want to be a female dancer?
왜 여성 댄서가 되고 싶나요?
Also don't understand anything.
또한 아무것도 이해하지 못합니다.
I see your makeup...
화장을 보니...
Unlike from the village,
마을과는 다르게,
Where are you from?
어디서 오셨나요?
Family from Yixing.
이싱(Yixing) 출신의 가족.
Why come to Shanghai?
상하이에 왜 왔나요?
Recently,
최근에,
my father died of illness.
아버지는 병으로 돌아가셨습니다.
My mother died when I was three years old.
나의 어머니는 내가 세 살 때 돌아가셨다.
I'm alone with no one to lean on
기댈 사람 하나 없이 혼자야
since
~부터
the Japanese came,
일본인이 왔고,
I also can't do business at the shop.
가게에서도 장사를 할 수 없어요.
I can only sell the house.
집만 팔 수 있어요.
He said he wanted to live with a distant cousin in Shanghai.
그는 상하이에서 먼 사촌과 함께 살고 싶다고 말했다.
But who would have thought that he had moved house.
그러나 그가 집을 옮겼다고 누가 생각이나 했겠는가.
I've been looking for him for two months, but haven't found him.
나는 그를 두 달 동안 찾았지만 찾지 못했습니다.
Rent money
돈을 임대
eat and drink
먹고 마시다
You also need money, right?
돈도 필요하잖아요?
Correct.
옳은.
I do have this money.
나에겐 이 돈이 있다.
Can't go on like this.
이렇게 계속할 수는 없습니다.
I saw in the movie,
영화에서 봤는데,
it is said that being a female dancer makes a lot of money.
여자 댄서가 되면 돈을 많이 번다고 하더라고요.
I just wanted to come here to try it, but unexpectedly.
그냥 여기 와서 먹어보고 싶었는데 의외로.
Here are the rules.
규칙은 다음과 같습니다.
Which must be considered.
고려해야 할 사항입니다.
How do I understand, I was even encouraged
어떻게 이해하지, 격려까지 받았지
by others.
다른 사람들에 의해.
Since childhood,
어린 시절부터,
I have never been treated unfairly like this.
나는 한 번도 이런 부당한 대우를 받은 적이 없습니다.
So this dancer also can't be careless.
그러니까 이 댄서도 방심할 수가 없어요.
How old is he?
그는 몇 살입니까?
Twenty.
이십.
Have good police.
좋은 경찰이 되세요.
Her face is also beautiful.
그녀의 얼굴도 아름답습니다.
So what dance can you dance?
그럼 어떤 춤을 출 수 있나요?
A little plan.
작은 계획.
Still have?
아직도 있나요?
No more.
더 이상은 없어.
Only slow three
천천히 3개만
waltz.
왈츠.
Blues
블루스
lemur.
여우 원숭이.
Tango.
탱고.
Exactly right
정확히 맞아요
just can't do it.
그냥 할 수 없습니다.
It's not serious.
심각하지 않습니다.
Don't be like that, brother.
그러지 마세요, 형제님.
I see you are a good person.
그러고 보니 당신은 좋은 사람이군요.
If not teach me.
가르쳐주지 않으면.
Teach you
가르쳐줘
then I have to pay school fees
그러면 내가 학비를 내야 해
no problem, there is money.
문제 없어요. 돈이 있어요.
How much is your tuition fee?
수업료는 얼마인가요?
You really want to learn, don't you?
당신은 정말로 배우고 싶어하지 않나요?
It's the same as us going to work
우리가 출근하는 것과 똑같아
one hour, two Yuan.
1시간 2위안.
Two Yuan.
2위안.
Good.
좋은.
Not expensive.
비싸지 않습니다.
So where do you want to study?
그럼 어디서 공부하고 싶나요?
To my house?
나의 집으로?
But the place is small,
하지만 장소가 협소해서
less than five square meters.
5제곱미터 미만.
There is also a bed and a table.
침대도 있고 테이블도 있어요.
So how do you dance?
그럼 춤은 어떻게 추나요?
Playing mahjong is not enough.
마작을 하는 것만으로는 충분하지 않습니다.
So how?
그래서 방법?
Let's make it like this
이렇게 만들어보자
come to my house
내 집에 와서
But
하지만
I have to time it outside
밖에서 시간을 보내야 해
one hour five Yuan
1시간 5위안
more than doubled.
두 배 이상.
You have to be clear,
분명히 해야 합니다.
aku Cai Hongling dulu di Bai Le Men
아쿠 카이 홍링 둘루 디 바이 르 멘
is in Bai Le Men
바이 르멘에 있어요
who queue to buy tickets
표를 사려고 줄을 선 사람
already lined up to the other side of the road.
이미 길 건너편에 줄을 서 있었어요.
Everyone came to support me.
모두가 나를 응원하러 왔어요.
Just think about it.
생각 해보세요.
If you spend this money now,
지금 이 돈을 쓰면
after you can dance the show
쇼에 맞춰 춤을 춘 후에
until the time there is a commission for dance tickets
댄스 티켓 커미션이 나올 때까지
there is a change in hourly rates.
시간당 요금에 변화가 있습니다.
The most unusual.
가장 특이한 것.
These are tips from customers.
고객이 알려주는 팁입니다.
Putting it in your bag isn't enough either.
가방에 넣는 것만으로는 충분하지 않습니다.
Very good.
매우 좋은.
sister,
자매,
today I want to study
오늘은 공부하고 싶어요
addicted man
중독된 남자
I tell you
나는 당신에게 말한다
I used to live in an apartment concession
나는 아파트 양수 지역에 살았습니다
at the time
당시
every month I can earn 200 Yuan more.
매달 200위안을 더 벌 수 있어요.
Kak Hong Ling.
카홍링.
Living alone?
혼자 사는?
I was so panicked this morning,
오늘 아침에 너무 당황해서,
I forgot to turn off the light.
나는 불을 끄는 것을 잊었다.
Later we will learn here
나중에 여기서 배우겠습니다.
there's new music, there's feelings
새로운 음악이 있고, 감정이 있어요
phonograph
축음기
expensive isn't it?
비싸지 않나요?
Not expensive, drizzle.
비싸지 않아, 이슬비.
What dance do you want to learn first?
어떤 춤을 먼저 배우고 싶나요?
Xiao San can do it.
샤오산은 할 수 있어요.
Then hurry up.
그럼 서둘러요.
No problem.
괜찮아요.
Three steps.
세 단계.
As the name suggests, each measure has three beats.
이름에서 알 수 있듯이 각 소절에는 3박자가 있습니다.
The rhythm is strong or weak.
리듬이 강하거나 약합니다.
But fast tempo three
하지만 빠른 템포 3
will be slower than you, San is much faster
너보다 느릴 텐데, San이 훨씬 빠르다
This is the Viennese Waltz.
비엔나 왈츠 입니다.
Classic fast dance
클래식 패스트 댄스
later I'll dance the man's step.
나중에 그 남자의 스텝에 맞춰 춤을 춰볼게요.
You follow me.
당신은 나를 따르십시오.
Here.
여기.
Danced almost 3 times.
거의 3번 정도 춤을 췄어요.
Male and female dance partners will be closer
남성과 여성의 댄스 파트너가 더 가까워집니다
start.
시작.
One two three.
하나 둘 셋.
Two, two, three.
둘, 둘, 셋.
When dancing almost three,
거의 3번 정도 춤을 출 때,
almost all the time it spins fast.
거의 항상 빠르게 회전합니다.
One two three.
하나 둘 셋.
Just fine?
괜찮나요?
sister,
자매,
maybe I'm too stupid.
어쩌면 내가 너무 멍청한 것일 수도 있습니다.
Footsteps were too fast, I was immediately confused.
발걸음이 너무 빨라서 순간 당황했다.
Maintain a rhythm, don't mess up your footsteps.
리듬을 유지하고 발자국을 어지럽히지 마십시오.
We continue.
우리는 계속합니다.
Road.
도로.
One two three.
하나 둘 셋.
Two, two, three.
둘, 둘, 셋.
Dance like this
이렇게 춤을 춰
is for your partner to control your rotation.
파트너가 회전을 제어하는 ​​것입니다.
So, quick three.
자, 빨리 3개요.
The dance that makes men control their pleasure the most.
남자의 쾌락을 가장 자제하게 만드는 춤.
Dizzy.
어지러운.
It's too dizzying.
너무 어지러워요.
I should probably take it slow
아마 천천히 해야 할 것 같아요
you rest for a while.
너는 잠시 쉬어라.
We will practice again later.
나중에 다시 연습하겠습니다.
Today's school fees
오늘의 학원비
faster slower than three times more tiring.
세 배 더 피곤한 것보다 더 빨리 더 느립니다.
It's still at this time tomorrow.
아직 내일 이 시간이에요.
I'm kind of stupid.
나는 좀 바보같아.
Sis Hong Ling, you have to be more careful.
홍링씨, 좀 더 조심해야 해요.
Don't worry, there's nothing I can't teach you.
걱정하지 마세요. 제가 가르쳐드릴 수 있는 것은 없습니다.
You're so good anyway
그래도 넌 참 착해
less than three months
3개월 미만
can definitely become the hottest female dancer in Shanghai Tan.
확실히 Shanghai Tan에서 가장 섹시한 여성 댄서가 될 수 있습니다.
Wait then
그럼 기다려
I will definitely not forget you.
나는 당신을 잊지 않을 것입니다.
Go ahead.
계속하세요.
For you.
당신을 위한.
Slowly.
느리게.
Who is she?
그녀는 누구입니까?
Haven't you heard?
못 들었어?
Learn to dance with me.
나와 함께 춤추는 법을 배워보세요.
Haven't I already said,
내가 이미 말하지 않았나요?
don't bring anyone home?
집에 아무도 안 데려오나요?
Every day buy medicine and food for you,
매일 약과 음식을 사주세요.
no need to spend money.
돈을 쓸 필요가 없습니다.
Besides, next month you have to pay rent again.
게다가 다음 달에도 집세를 다시 내야 해요.
Where does the money come from?
돈은 어디서 나오나요?
if you become a female dancer calmly,
차분하게 여자 댄서가 된다면
and don't go Pai Jiu bet,
그리고 Pai Jiu 내기에는 가지 마세요.
Why should it be this way?
왜 이렇게 되어야 할까요?
Are you still blaming me?
아직도 나를 비난하고 있나요?
Don't underestimate that girl.
그 여자를 과소평가하지 마세요.
Too much money.
너무 많은 돈.
After I succeeded in getting this business,
이 사업을 성공시킨 후,
we don't need to worry about food and drink,
우리는 먹고 마시는 것에 대해 걱정할 필요가 없습니다.
and care about that little money.
그리고 그 작은 돈에 관심을 가져라.
You talked for so long,
너무 오랫동안 얘기하셨는데,
also don't talk about what business
그리고 어떤 사업에 대해서도 이야기하지 마세요
Also don't talk to anyone.
또한 아무에게도 말하지 마십시오.
What can I expect from you?
내가 당신에게서 무엇을 기대할 수 있나요?
I told you to throw things in the trash
내가 물건을 쓰레기통에 버리라고 했잖아
have you thrown it away?
버렸어?
I'm very tired today.
오늘은 매우 피곤해요.
Tomorrow it's thrown again, it's not the same
내일 또 던져져 예전 같지 않아
what if the woman saw it?
여자가 봤다면 어떡하지?
Look, okay?
보세요, 알았죠?
Stupid!
멍청한!
You didn't hear what I said.
당신은 내가 말한 것을 듣지 못했습니다.
If she didn't come to learn to dance,
만약 그녀가 춤을 배우러 오지 않았다면,
do you know now the CCP and its military power
지금 중국 공산당과 그 군사력을 아시나요?
is hunting me.
나를 사냥하고 있어요.
He... Where could he be
그 사람은...그 사람은 어디에 있을까?
I ask you,
나는 당신에게 묻습니다.
will he come tomorrow?
그 사람 내일 올까?
We've agreed.
우리는 동의했습니다.
Will come.
올 것이다.
Tomorrow night,
내일 밤,
kill him.
그를 죽여.
You're crazy
넌 미쳤어
I can't commit murder.
나는 살인을 저지를 수 없습니다.
So do you still want to come with me?
그럼 아직도 나와 함께 가고 싶니?
I can't kill people either.
나도 사람을 못 죽인다.
Take it.
가져.
Tomorrow night,
내일 밤,
you told him,
당신이 그에게 말했어요.
Do you want to eat late at night first?
먼저 밤늦게 먹을래?
Then, look for a quiet street.
그런 다음 조용한 거리를 찾으십시오.
While he wasn't paying attention,
그 사람이 관심을 기울이지 않는 동안,
when he wasn't paying attention.
그가 주의를 기울이지 않았을 때.
Even if no one is looking
아무도 찾지 않아도
Gunshots will also be heard.
총소리도 들립니다.
Then you
그럼 당신은
past the old factory road.
오래된 공장길을 지나
There was no one there.
거기에는 아무도 없었습니다.
Moving on the road.
도로로 이동합니다.
do you know
당신은 알고 있나요
this thing in my hand
내 손에 있는 이것
absolutely priceless
정말 귀중한
so now we
그래서 지금 우리는
must be very careful
매우 조심해야 한다
there can be no fault at all
전혀 잘못이 있을 수 없다
why are you dressed like this?
왜 이런 옷을 입고 있나요?
What are you going to do?
당신은 무엇을 할 예정입니까?
Just got home this night, still dressed like this.
오늘 밤에 막 집에 왔는데도 여전히 이런 옷을 입고 있어요.
Still so fragrant
그래도 너무 향기로워
Why?
왜?
Allowing you not to come home all night.
밤새도록 집에 오지 못하게 하려고요.
Haven't answered my question yet.
내 질문에 아직 대답하지 않았습니다.
Good.
좋은.
Then I answer honestly.
그러면 솔직하게 대답하겠습니다.
One
하나
ballroom dancing
볼룸 댄스
happy
행복하다
I forgot the time, so I came home late.
시간을 잊어버려서 집에 늦게 돌아왔어요.
Two
둘
dressed like this.
이런 옷을 입고.
Certainly
틀림없이
Want to ask me to dance.
나에게 춤을 청하고 싶다.
Three, what is that?
셋, 그게 뭐야?
Why is it so fragrant
왜 이렇게 향기롭지?
delicious or not?
맛있지 않니?
From France?
프랑스에서요?
The aroma is delicious.
향기가 맛있습니다.
But this dance hall
그런데 이 댄스홀은
you...
너...
Isn't it unsuitable to go?
가기에는 부적합하지 않나요?
Why can't I go?
왜 갈 수 없나요?
You feel that my face is not good
내 얼굴이 좋지 않다고 느끼나요?
or my body?
아니면 내 몸?
But my status is not good.
그런데 상태가 좋지 않아요.
You see, you are my wife.
알다시피, 당신은 내 아내입니다.
Married
기혼
young woman,
젊은 여성,
next time you want to go, you can tell me.
다음에 가고 싶으면 나한테 말해줘.
I'll accompany you.
제가 동행하겠습니다.
I suddenly remembered one sentence
문득 한 문장이 떠올랐다
I told you, there are people,
말했잖아, 사람들이 있다고
in the heart
마음 속에
small braids have not been cut neatly.
작은 땋은 머리가 깔끔하게 잘리지 않았습니다.
What is meant is you
무슨 뜻인가요?
still accompanies me to the dance hall
아직도 댄스홀에 나를 따라다녀
I heard you accompanied that big artist
그 대작가와 동행했다고 들었는데
didn't come home overnight.
밤새 집에 오지 않았다.
Don't be angry yet.
아직 화내지 마세요.
True, or not?
사실인가요, 아닌가요?
I'm just worried about a friend.
그냥 친구가 걱정이에요.
Then you tell me.
그럼 당신이 나에게 말해.
Who are you going with?
누구 랑가?
Male or female?
남자야, 여자야?
You guess.
당신은 추측.
Look at it.
보세요.
Look, aren't you angry?
봐, 화나지 않았어?
You must be taking revenge on me yesterday,
어제 나한테 복수했겠구나.
han Lu, ya?
한루, 응?
I don't care about that at all.
나는 그것에 대해 전혀 신경 쓰지 않습니다.
I just feel
난 그냥 느낌
even though they are husband and wife?
부부인데도요?
After married
결혼 후
must also enjoy absolute freedom.
또한 절대적인 자유를 누려야 합니다.
No one needs to interfere
누구도 간섭할 필요가 없어
True, or not?
사실인가요, 아닌가요?
Correct.
옳은.
Wait.
기다리다.
I haven't asked you yet.
아직 물어보지 않았어요.
Why was the door lock also replaced?
도어락도 교체한 이유는 무엇인가요?
From now on
지금부터
I sleep on the bed, you sleep on the sofa.
나는 침대에서 자고, 당신은 소파에서 자요.
Why?
왜?
Then I sleep on the sofa.
그런 다음 소파에서 자요.
Don't.
하지 않다.
Don't, don't.
하지 마세요.
You... sleep in bed. you sleep in bed.
당신은... 침대에서 자요. 당신은 침대에서 잔다.
I sleep on the sofa.
나는 소파에서 잔다.
I want to sleep on the sofa.
소파에서 자고 싶어요.
Which key is this?
이것은 어떤 열쇠입니까?
This?
이것?
Shanghai's nightlife is truly rich.
상하이의 밤문화는 정말 풍부합니다.
I used to live in vain.
나는 헛되이 살았습니다.
According to you,
당신에 따르면,
What cheongsam should I wear tomorrow?
내일은 어떤 치파오를 입을까?
Are you still going tomorrow?
내일 아직도 가시나요?
Guoguo, you are taking revenge on me.
Guoguo, 당신은 나에게 복수하고 있습니다.
Deliberately making me angry, huh?
일부러 나를 화나게 만드는 거죠?
Don't blame me for telling the truth.
내가 진실을 말했다고 비난하지 마세요.
You're the one wearing this Cheongsam,
이 치파오를 입은 사람이 바로 당신이에요.
in Shanghai is out of date.
상하이에서는 구식입니다.
You wear this outfit to the ballroom
넌 이 옷을 입고 연회장에 가
people will count
사람들은 셀 것이다
You're just a country girl selling flowers.
당신은 꽃을 파는 시골 소녀일 뿐입니다.
Straight?
똑바로?
I'll tell you how to spray perfume
향수 뿌리는 방법을 알려드릴게요
sprinkle a drop
한 방울을 뿌린다
That's an angel
저 사람은 천사야
two drops, that's called sexy.
두 방울, 그걸 섹시하다고 부르죠.
Like you spilled a bottle all over him,
당신이 그 사람 몸에 병을 쏟은 것처럼,
they must think you are a dew flower seller.
그 사람들은 당신이 이슬꽃 파는 사람이라고 생각하는 게 틀림없어요.
And most importantly
그리고 가장 중요한 것은
in a Shanghai dance hall
상하이 댄스홀에서
11 o'clock is the gold field.
11시가 금밭이다.
What about the beautiful women?
아름다운 여성들은 어떻습니까?
After dancing on the golden field,
황금빛 들판에서 춤을 춘 뒤,
they have disbanded.
그들은 해체되었습니다.
Like this just came back.
이렇게 방금 돌아왔습니다.
Certainly no one had invited before
확실히 이전에는 아무도 초대한 적이 없었습니다.
too sorry
너무 미안해
chen Jia Ping
첸 지아 핑
I tell you, I was angry
내가 말했잖아, 난 화가 났어
If you're angry, you...
화가 나면 당신은...
And Han Lu didn't come home overnight.
그리고 한루는 밤새 집에 돌아오지 않았습니다.
Irritating.
화나게 하는.
Shameless.
뻔뻔한.
Never mind, this fuss
신경 쓰지 마, 이 소란은
in a long time,
오랫동안,
can keep your distance
거리를 유지할 수 있다
I hope he's not really mad at me.
그 사람이 나한테 정말 화난 게 아니길 바라요.
And also,
그리고 또한,
Don't take my things carelessly.
내 물건을 함부로 가져가지 마세요.
What's that?
그게 뭐야?
Placed under the mattress.
매트리스 아래에 배치됩니다.
It's all a thought
다 생각일 뿐이야
prevention of the main danger to peaceful government.
평화로운 정부에 대한 주요 위험을 예방합니다.
Don't look at it carelessly
함부로 보지 마세요
who wants to see?
누가 보고 싶어?
I sleep.
나는 잔다.
Eavesdropping?
도청?
He thought I couldn't see.
그는 내가 볼 수 없다고 생각했습니다.
Good night.
안녕히 주무세요.
Enough already.
이미 충분합니다.
This time there was a problem,
이번에 문제가 생겼는데,
I've been on duty for the past few days...
지난 며칠간 근무 중이었는데...
No problem.
괜찮아요.
Did he reconcile or betray?
그는 화해했는가 아니면 배신했는가?
Hey.
여기요.
Yumo Painting and Calligraphy Shop.
Yumo 그림과 서예 가게.
Good.
좋은.
Old friends,
오랜 친구,
everyone coming?
다들 오나요?
Two punctures
두 개의 구멍
section chief Chen
첸 과장
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
Dry grass.
건초.
Why are there still people in the dry grass?
왜 마른 풀밭에 아직도 사람이 있는 걸까요?
Yesterday
어제
Captain Zhao, they arrested a CCP member.
자오 대위님, 그들은 중국 공산당원을 체포했습니다.
Is dead
죽었어
he asked me to take it out.
그는 나에게 그것을 꺼내달라고 요청했습니다.
It's sad.
슬프다.
Two punctures.
두 개의 구멍이 있습니다.